Fuel economy data is collected from vehicle testing at
يتم جمع بيانات اقتصاد الوقود من اختبارات المركبات
EPA's National Vehicle and Fuel Emissions Lab in Ann Arbor, Michigan.
في المعمل القومي لانبعاثات المركبات والوقود التابع لوكالة حماية الطاقة الأمريكية في مدينة آن أربور بولاية ميتشيجان.
The EPA provides this data to the government each year,
تقدم وكالة حماية الطاقة الأمريكية هذه البيانات للحكومة سنويًا،
which the Department of Energy uses to publish their fuel economy guide.
وتستخدمها وزارة الطاقة في نشر دليلها لاقتصاد الوقود.
This data is available for download.
هذه البيانات متاحة للتنزيل.
You'll be analyzing data sets that are downloaded here,
سوف تحللون مجموعات البيانات المُنزَّلة هنا
for 2018 and 2008.
لعامي 2018 و2008.
Here are the data sets for 2008 and 2018 in a Jupyter notebook.
ها هي مجموعات البيانات لعامي 2008 و2018 في دفتر ملاحظات Jupyter.
There are probably a few features here that don't make too much sense to you.
ربما توجد بضع سمات هنا لا تبدو منطقية جدًا بالنسبة لكم.
Before analyzing the data sets,
قبل تحليل مجموعات البيانات،
you should take some time to understand this data and how it was collected.
عليكم استغراق بعض الوقت في فهم هذه البيانات وكيفية جمعها.
Luckily, there's good documentation for this.
لحسن الحظ، هناك توثيق جيد لهذا.
On the bottom of this page,
في أسفل هذه الصفحة،
there are two links to documentation for this data.
يوجد رابطان لتوثيق لهذه البيانات.
This link downloads the readme file,
ينزِّل هذا الرابط ملف readme
that provides some details about the data.
والذي يقدم بعض التفاصيل حول البيانات،
And this leads to documentation in a PDF that's
وهذا يقودكم إلى التوثيق الموجود في ملف PDF
a bit clearer and more specific to the data set you'll be analyzing.
أوضح بقليل وأكثر خصوصية لمجموعة البيانات التي ستحللونها.
It even has helpful links that provide more information about these features.
يتضمن هذا الملف أيضًا روابط مفيدة توفر مزيدًا من المعلومات حول هذه السمات.
You'll be using this documentation to answer
ستستخدمون هذا التوثيق للإجابة
some questions about this data set in the next section.
عن بعض الأسئلة حول مجموعة البيانات هذه في القسم التالي.